翻译: 曾小威 小鸡
*外面的天气真可怕*
*Oh, the weather outside is frightful*
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
我给每一个人都织了袜子
I made everyone stockings.
校对: 西西
Lillian
Lillian.
Titus
Titus.
后期: 尘世劫
我自己
Yours truly.
Mimi
Mimi.
还有Murasaki
And Murasaki.
Murasaki不过圣诞节
Murasaki doesn't do Christmas.
压制: 肉包超人
天啊 我爱圣诞节
Gosh, I love Christmas:
听着音乐 拆开礼物
the music, untangling things,
在室外张灯结彩 在室内布置圣诞树
putting lights outdoors and trees indoors.
还有什么
Say what?
我们欢聚一堂 为如此多美好的事情庆祝
And we're all together with so much to celebrate:
非同一般的友谊和全新的人生冒险
special friendships and new adventures
最后再说一句 "再见"
and giving a final "Later, gator"
让烦恼属于过往
to the problems of yester--
嗝往
Yester-- urp.
你听到了
You heard me.
亲爱的 你应该去看医生
Honey, you should see a doctor.
这味道好像是你体内死了一只老鼠
It's like a mouse died in the walls of your body.
嗬 嗬 嗬
Ho, ho, ho!
祝你们所有人圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas to all of youse!
圣诞老人
Santa?
Santa.
我不能亲吻你 我已经结婚了
Oh, I can't kiss you. I'm married.
那些犹太人夺走了我的画
The Jews took my painting.
现在才是真正的派对
Now it's a party.
嗬 嗬 嗬 你这个贱人
Ho, ho, ho. You ho.
Sonja
Sonja?
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you.
三 个 月 前
这件破事发生之前的三个月
Three months earlier on this mess...
自从我看到这家店的名字叫"迷你汉堡"
I've been wanting to bring you to this place
我就一直想带你来
ever since I saw it was called Sliderz.
不过 我要向你道歉
I apologize, though.
店名Sliderz意为迷你汉堡 同时slides有滑梯的意思
其实这里并没有任何"滑梯"
There aren't actually any slides in here.
但是看看这些迷你汉堡
But look at these tiny hamburgers.
它们使你感觉像个巨人
They make you feel like a giant.
我要一口吃掉你
I'm gonna eat you up in one bite.
"求求你 不要吃我 我还有家人"
"Please, no, I have a family."
这太有意思了 Kimmy
This is so fun, Kimmy.
我很高兴我逃离了我的绿卡婚姻
I'm so glad I ran away from my green card marriage
继续跟你约会
to go on dates with you.
我是素食主义者
I'm a vegan.
慢着 你刚才说什么
Wait, what did you say?
我说 "我是素食主义者"
I said, "I'm a vegan."
我以为当我们在5公里动物权益公益跑
I thought you knew that
相遇的时候 你就已经知道这件事了
when we met at that animal rights 5K.
我还以为那活动是为了让动物们可以自由结婚
Oh, I thought that was so animals could marry each other.
我觉得这次约会进展得
Well, I think this date is going...
好讨厌
Hated it.
这很困难 是因为
Oh, it's hard because
你还跟你的前任藕断丝连
you're still hung up on your ex.
我能理解
I get it.
我还会回想起我的初恋 Bobby
I still think about my first love, Bobby.
我们曾经一起参加罗斯福岛的夏令营
We went to summer camp together on Roosevelt Island.
小Bobby Durst
Little Bobby Durst.
我为他倾倒
He was my first crush.
就是字面意思 他想要击倒我
Literally, he tried to crush me.
我等了15年才重新恢复自己的生活
It's just, I waited 15 years to get my life back,
后来我找到了工作 找到了男朋友
and then I got a job, I got a boyfriend,
然后这个世界好像在对我说 "你神经病啊"
but then the world was like, "Psych!"
我理解 亲爱的 你现在就想得到全部
I know, dear, you want it all right now:
美满事业 如意郎君
the career, the husband,
还有泪滴纹身
the teardrop tattoo.
但是 先去寻欢作乐吧
But hey, have a little fun for five minutes.
让我带你出去
Hey, let me take you out.
我可是撩汉好队友
Ooh, I'm a great wingman.
男人们发现我非常容易亲近
Men find me very approachable
因为我有一双大眼睛
because my eyes are large
而且我的头发长得像好看的意面
and my hair is like beautiful spaghetti.
我可以把他们钓上钩
I get 'em on the hook.
然后我们悄悄地在饮料里下摇头丸
Then we'll slip 'em a disco biscuit
再偷偷地把饮料换给他们
and pull a switcheroo.
双关: Timberlake曾是男子组合NSYNC的一员
跟上我的步伐 Kimberlake 我要去离婚
Get 'NSYNC, Kimberlake. I got to go get divorced.
今晚我们要大肆狂欢
Oh, we're gonna paint the town red tonight.
两个问题
Ooh, two questions.
你喜欢西班牙小伙子吗 还有 你会滑旱冰吗
Do you like Spanish guys, and can you roller-skate?
喜欢 只接受正面体位
Yes, but only frontways.
可能会吧
And probably.
慢着 我说的是"可能喜欢 只会向前滑"
Oh, wait, I said that backwards.
*坚不可摧*
*Unbreakable*
*她们活下来了 卧槽*
*They alive, damn it*
*真是个奇迹*
*It's a miracle*
*坚不可摧*
*Unbreakable*
*她们活下来了 卧槽*
*They alive, damn it*
*但是女人可真牛逼啊*
*But females are strong as hell*
*坚不可摧*
*Unbreakable*
*她们活下来了 卧槽*
*They alive, damn it*
*真是个奇迹*
*It's a miracle*
*坚不可摧*
*Unbreakable*
*她们活下来了 卧槽*
*They alive, damn it*
*接下来是*
*That's gonna be, uh...*
我  本  坚  强
第二季        第一集
*那个 华丽的变身*
*you know, uh，a fascinating transition.*
电波诚译
*卧槽*
*Damn it*
你的房子在那边 呆子
Hey, your house is that way, dummy.
我的天啊 谢谢你
Oh, my God, thank you.
我已经站在这里好几个小时了
I've been standing here for hours.
小心点 我在那边拉了粑粑
Watch out. I pooped over there.
根据Wilkerson太太提供的证书
So, according to the license presented by Mrs. Wilkerson,
你们俩是在1998年6月6日结婚的
you two were married on June 6, 1998.
这也能叫结婚
Barely.
Ronald Ephen Wilkerson 你是否愿意
And do you, Ronald Ephen Wilkerson,
娶这位女子为你的合法妻子
take this woman to be your lawfully wedded wife?
好吧
Mm-kay.
而且Wilkerson太太声称你在1998年6月6日
And Mrs. Wilkerson claims that you abandoned her
抛弃了她
on June 6, 1998.
等一下
Wait a minute.
那是同一天
That's the same day.
是吗 我不清楚
Is it? I wouldn't know.
你甚至在我们跳第一支舞之前就离开了
You left before we even did our first dance.
而且你知道我们的编舞非常完美
And you know our choreography was on point.
你没有一次能接住我
Mm, you dropped me every time.
我还以为你至少是跟一个男的跑了
I thought at least you ran away to be with a man.
但是你却在这里
But here you are,
占一个傻女孩的便宜
taking advantage of some other goofy girl
她穿得像个他妈的史酷比狗
dressed like she's on Scooby damn Doo.
谢谢
Thank you.
真没想到啊 Ronald
I can't believe you, Ronald.
不要叫我Ronald
Do not call me Ronald.
Rah-nald
Rah-nald.
你以为你可以安然无恙地脱身吗
You think you can walk away from your problems?
好了 我找到你了
Well, I found you,
我要起诉你 要求你赔偿17年的配偶赡养费
and I'm gonna sue you for 17 years' worth of spousal support,
还有400美元的婚礼费用
$400 for the wedding itself,
我还要拿回我的新娘外套
and I want my bridal jacket back.
我要夺走你所拥有的一切 Ronald Wilkerson
I'm gonna take everything you got, Ronald Wilkerson.
真的吗 Titus
Really, Titus?
你还要再逃一次吗
You're just gonna run away from her again?
我听说蒙特利尔有一个充满活力的戏剧舞台
I hear Montreal has a vibrant theater scene,
再见了 亲爱的
so au revoir, les Felicieuses.
或许去和Vonda谈一下就好了
Maybe just go talk to Vonda.
你完全没和她说过话 你们可是夫妻哎
You haven't spoken to her at all, and you guys were married.
Kim 你不明白
Kim, you don't understand.
对我来说 密西西比州就是一个坑
Mississippi was my bunker.
摩奇: 一种新型有机覆盖物
我从周一开始忙活Vonda她舅舅的摩奇生意
I start work Monday at Vonda's uncle's mulch business.
你说什么
What's that you said?
我说我从周一开始忙活Vonda她舅舅的摩奇生意
I said I start work Monday at Vonda's uncle's mulch business.
啥
What now?
我从周一开始 忙活Vonda她舅舅的摩奇生意
I start work Monday... at Vonda's uncle's mulch business.
什么 亲爱的
What, dear?
我说我是一个恐慌症发作的同性恋
I said I'm a homosexual having a panic attack.
这岂不是美妙极了
Oh, isn't that wonderful?
接下来
And now,
让我们欢迎这对新人到舞池中央来
please welcome to the dance floor
他们将开启人生中的第二个也是最后一个阶段
as they begin this second and final part of their lives,
有请Ronald Wilkerson夫妇
Mr. And Mrs. Ronald Wilkerson!
你不就是Ronald Wilkerson吗
Aren't you Ronald Wilkerson?
是说我吗 不是 先生
Who me? No, sir.
我是
I'm...
Titus Andromedon
Titus Andromedon.
Ronald Wilkerson 请你现身
Ronald Wilkerson, show your face.
我鼓起了最大的勇气去逃跑
It took all the courage I had to escape.
Titus使我避免了那种除了小孩就是摩奇的生活
Titus saved me from a life of babies and mulch.
现在Vonda要夺走我所创造的美好世界
Now Vonda's gonna take away this beautiful world I built for my--
该死的蠹虫
Damn silverfish.
如果我去跟Vonda谈呢
What if I go talk to Vonda?
或许我可以打动她
Maybe I could get through to her,
这是两个女人之间的交流
woman to woman.
恶
Ew.
我会带她出去吃冰淇淋
I'll take her out for ice cream.
有甜筒在手上总不会生气了吧
You can't be mad with a cone in your paw.
好吧 但是以防万一 我要继续收拾东西
Okay, but just in case, I'm gonna keep on packing,
至少也要等到我的血糖降下来
at least until my blood sugar drops.
降了降了
There it is.
今天我们在这里向我们之中的一员表示祝贺
We are here today to celebrate one of our own,
Anthony Black Elk
Anthony Black Elk,
他将在几天后去达特茅斯学院上学
who's going away to Dartmouth College in a few days.
不要去当傻逼曲棍球运动员
Don't become some d-bag lacrosse player.
亲爱的 是我们发明了曲棍球
Honey, we invented lacrosse.
我不能认同
I don't think that's right.
Anthony 这神圣的烟斗
Anthony, this sacred pipe,
名叫chanunpa
the chanunpa,
是九代之前雕刻成的
was carved nine generations ago.
它在翁迪德尼战役中幸存了下来
It survived Wounded Knee,
我们曾经用它来为越南战争中的兄弟们祈祷
and we used it to pray for our brothers in Vietnam.
而今天我们将呼唤伟大的神灵
And today we will ask the Great Spirit--
这他妈的是什么
What the holy hell is this?
这是电子烟 爸爸
It's a tobacco vape, Dad.
Katherine Heigl: 美国女演员
Katherine Heigl也抽这烟
Katherine Heigl uses one.
吸烟有害健康啊 各位
Smoking kills, you guys.
神圣烟斗在哪里 Jackie Lynn
Where is that pipe, Jackie Lynn?
我把烟斗举在空中 它被一只鹰叼走了
I held it in the air, and a hawk took it.
Jackie Lynn
Jackie Lynn...
好吧 烟斗在棋盘游戏后面的壁橱里
Oh, fine, it's in the hall closet behind the board games.
老烟枪
Addict.
谁在那里
Who is that?
Jackie Lynn 戴上你的隐形眼镜吧
Jackie Lynn, just use your contact lenses.
你需要按照医生的处方去做
You need the prescription.
不 妈妈
No, Mom.
它们会使我的眼睛变蓝的
They turn my eyes blue.
而且他们通过飞行射击游戏和对口型大作战
And that's me giving in to white culture,
使我向白人文化屈服
with their drone wars and lip-sync battles.
那就买没有颜色的嘛
Well, then order plain ones.
昨天我看到你在给雄野牛挤奶
Yesterday I saw you try to milk a male buffalo.
无所谓 妈妈
Whatever, Mom.
我挤出来了 放到冰箱里了
It worked. I put it in the fridge.
那你准备什么时候
And when are you gonna
把你开来的那辆警车还回去
give back that police car you showed up in?
里面住着一只浣熊
There's a raccoon living in it.
它已经死了
Oh, he's not living in it.
原理同儿童锁
囚犯锁起了作用 它被关在了警车后面
He got stuck in the back because of the prisoner locks
然后它中暑死了
and he died of heatstroke.
我知道你是好心
I know you mean well,
但不要再来帮忙了
but just stop trying to help.
但是我想帮忙
But I want to help.
我只是想尽到自己
All I want is to be the daughter
作为女儿的本分
I should have been this whole time.
告诉我我能做什么 我不会让你们失望的
Just tell me what I can do, and I won't let you down.
我保证
I promise.
好吧 你可以走远一点 到田地去
Well, you could go far, far in the fields
去跳超级特别而且非常重要的丰收舞蹈
and do the harvest super special important dance.
听起来好重要
That sounds important.
我会教你怎么跳
I'll teach it to you.
谢谢
Thank you.
再见
Aloha.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
听着 我之所以打电话叫你出来
Look, the reason I called
是因为Titus 讨厌
is 'cause Titus-- Dang!
快舔干净
Lick it.
你有什么事吗
What's your deal?
你简直就像个卡通人物
You're like a cartoon person.
说实话 我不是真的想要Ronald的钱
Honestly, I don't even really want money from Ronald.
我只是想让他道歉
I just want him to apologize.
这样做可能会使我看上去像个傻瓜 Kimmy
This might make me seem like a fool, Kimmy,
但我们曾爱过彼此
but we loved each other.
我知道我们曾经爱过
I know we did.
我是说 我早就知道他喜欢男人
I mean, I knew he liked men.
Tim Meadows: 美国黑人男演员
有请Tim Meadows
With Tim Meadows...
但是他也知道我喜欢苗条的白人小子
But he knew I liked skinny white boys.
David Spade: 美国白人男演员
David Spade
...David Spade.
Hootie & the Blowfish: 男子音乐组合 成员有白人有黑人
音乐表演嘉宾 Hootie & the Blowfish
Musical guest: Hootie & the Blowfish.
我们都无法在奇克索县做真实的自己
Neither of us could live our truth in Chickasaw County.
所以我想 "我们将一起生活在谎言之中"
So I thought, "We gonna live our lie together."
但是那天晚上 我们婚礼那天晚上
But that night, our wedding night,
当大家意识到Ronald已经逃走了的时候
when they realized Ronald ran away,
抚养他长大成人的五个姑妈
every one of his five aunties that raised him
统统都心脏病发作了
had a heart attack.
他将我抛弃在舞池中 我独自一人
And he left me on that dance floor, alone,
别无选择 只好一路跳着机械舞回到了车里
with no choice but to Robocop my way to the car.
太糟糕了
That's terrible.
Ronald Wilkerson永远不会对我做那种事
Ronald Wilkerson would have never done that to me.
是你的朋友Titus干的
That was your friend Titus.
我甚至都认不出他来了
I don't even recognize that man.
无论怎样 他确实填充过脸颊 不过失败了
For what it's worth, he did get cheek implants that slipped.
你会重蹈我的覆辙
You're the new me.
看看现在的你 还在想办法收拾他的烂摊子
Look at you right now, trying to clean up his mess.
一旦你变得对他没有利用价值
But once there's nothing else that Titus can get from you,
他就会甩下一张待付的牙医账单和满满一冰箱
he will leave you with an unpaid dental bill
变质了的婚宴虾仁 然后离你而去
and a refrigerator full of spoiled wedding shrimp.
小心你的背后
Watch your back.
快去洗手吧 宝贝
And wash your arm, baby.
你为什么迟到
Why are you late?
为什么律师先生要召开紧急会议
Why did Mr. Lawyer call an emergency meeting?
是Vonda干的好事吗
Did Vonda do this?
Titus 你放她鸽子的把戏
Titus, the way you bailed on her,
还在别人身上用过吗
have you ever done that to anyone else?
一张山姆古迪商店的信用卡没还
A Sam Goody credit card.
放弃了我的大学橄榄球奖学金
My college football scholarship.
还离开了长得比我帅的表弟 大傻瓜Darius
My cousin who got handsomer than me-- Stupid Darius.
还有 我不会付钱给这个律师
Also, I'm not gonna pay this lawyer.
好吧 我有一个好消息 一个坏消息
Well, I've got good news, and I've got bad news.
坏消息是 Instagram删除了我的账号
The bad news is, Instagram canceled my account
理由是我缺乏兴趣
due to lack of interest.
好消息是
The good news is that
早在2008年 Ronald Wilkerson就已经在法律上被宣布死亡
in 2008, Ronald Wilkerson was declared legally dead...
就是她宣布的
by this woman!
当时他已经失踪十年了
He'd been missing ten years.
他饮食那么不健康 十年都给多了
With his diet, I was being generous.
够犀利
Sick burn.
然而
However,
你不仅领取了Wilkerson先生的社保收入
you did collect Mr. Wilkerson's Social Security earnings,
而且获取了他为自己双腿投保
as well as the money from an insurance policy
所得的收入
he took out on his legs.
Mary Hart: 美国电视女主持人 为美腿投保百万美金
我那时受到了Mary Hart的启发
I was inspired by Mary Hart
为我的资产投保
to insure my assets at that time.
因为"Ronald Wilkerson"已经死了
So because "Ronald Wilkerson" is dead,
所以你不能起诉他 Brooks女士
Ms. Brooks, you can't sue him.
事实上 你还欠他大约500美元
As a matter of fact, you may owe him about $500.
- 什么  - 什么
- What? - What?
好吧 我认为我们的会议结束了
Well, I think we're done here.
砰 贱人
Boom, bitch!
拜拜
Bye!
别跟我作对
I am not the one.
报纸的幽默版块见 乡巴佬
See you in the funny papers, Country Mouse.
Jennife Love Hewitt: 女演员 曾出演美剧<鬼语者>
Phil Rizzuto: 已故职业棒球明星 曾给贷款品牌做代言人
你最好打电话给Jennifer Love Hewitt和Phil Rizzuto吧
You better call Jennifer Love Hewitt and Phil Rizzuto,
因为你欠鬼魂的钱
because you owe a ghost money.
祝你好运 Kimmy
Good luck with that, Kimmy.
Lillian 你觉得Titus会像对待Vonda那样
Lillian, do you think Titus would ever do to us
对待我们吗
what he did to Vonda?
把饼干嚼碎 然后在舞会结束后假装吐在我们身上
Chew up crackers and pretend to throw up on us after prom
以此来避免跟别人上床吗
to get out of sex?
可以预见 没错
I could see it happening, yes.
但是谁在乎呢
But who cares?
我们出去浪
We're going out.
讽刺美国国家安全局监听民众电话的行径
我们拿到的电话号码会比国安局的还要多
We're gonna get more phone numbers than the NSA.
政治手段
Political!
是的 没错
Yes! Right.
让我们享受人生
Let's go life.
等等 我要进里面买点东西
Oh, wait, I need something in here.
我去内衣那边看看
Oh, I'll be in intimates.
嗨 我要一盒杀虫药
Hi, I need a box of silverfish poison.
没有了 抱歉 女士 那家伙买了最后一盒
No, sorry, ma'am. That guy's buy the last one.
Kimmy
Kimmy?
Dong
Dong.
你看起来不错
You look well.
很高兴见到你
It's so nice to see you.
我也想见你
I'd like that.
你老婆怎么样了
How is your wife?
还是Sonja吗
Still Sonja?
是啊 谢谢
Yes, thank you.
我和Sonja明天要请人吃早午餐
Sonja and I are having people over for brunch tomorrow,
但是蠹虫把我们的毛巾都咬烂了
and the silverfish ate all our towels.
你的英语说得真溜
Wow, your English is getting really well.
谢谢
Thank you.
再也没有你来帮我学英语了
I didn't have you to help me anymore,
所以我看了很多集
so I started watching a lot of...
<与卡戴珊姐妹同行>
Keeping Up with the Kardashians.
好啊 有效果了
Well, it's working.
你真好
Aw, you're sweet.
Dong
Dong?
天啊
My God.
你应该跟我们一起去滑旱冰
You should come roller-skating with us.
什么 Lillian 不行
What? Lillian, no.
大家都知道三个人一起你就不会滑了
Everyone knows you can't skate as a threesies.
闭嘴
Shut up.
运气好的话 我们可能会来个四人行
As luck would have it, we'll be a foursome.
我刚碰见我的老情人Bobby了
I just ran into my old flame, Bobby.
好的 你们好
Okay, hi-hi.
我想Dong该回去他老婆身边了 Lillian
I think Dong probably needs to get back to his wife, Lillian.
其实 Sonja去上比克拉姆热瑜伽课了
Actually, Sonja's at her Bikram hot yoga class,
而且在释放杀虫药之后的7个小时里
and I do have to stay out of the apartment
我都不能进屋
for seven hours after I set off the silverfish bomb.
所以呢 那提议太棒了
So, yeah, that sounds amazing.
完美
Well, perfect.
我们来个四人行
We'll be a foursome.
来吧
Come on.
我想要这个
I want this.
你想要才怪
Like you do.
你说得对 我是错的
You're right. I'm wrong.
*你可以感受它的存在*
*You can feel it*
*它会保佑我们*
*It protects us*
*我扭 我扭 我扭扭扭*
*Boogie oogie oogie oogie.*
*向玉米之神祈祷*
*Pray to the corn god*
*他是电动玉米*
*He's corn-lectric*
你为什么要跳
Why are you doing the...
白人傻瓜的
White idiot
婚礼舞蹈
wedding dance...
白人傻瓜
White idiot?
我的玉米之神啊
Oh, my corn god.
早午饭 对吗
So a brunch, huh?
Frasier: 美剧<欢乐一家亲>的主人公
像Frasier那样高雅
That's Frasier fancy.
这只是为了给移民局官员留下好印象
It's just to impress the immigration officer.
我和Sonja的婚姻必须真实可信 而且要满两年
Sonja and I have to be believably married for two years,
这样我就可以成为真正的美国人 然后和她离婚
and then I'll be a real American and get divorced.
我们聊点别的吧
Let's talk about something else.
我觉得Khloe
Mm, I think Khloe
可能是卡戴珊家族中最聪明的一个
is probably the smartest of the Kardashians
因为 她最理智
'cause, like, she makes the most sense.
我从来没有看过她们的节目
I've never seen their show.
Kim Kardashian以丰乳肥臀闻名
我只知道Kim是个翘臀明星
I just know that Kim is a butt star
指美国饶舌歌手 Kanye West
嫁给了一个痛恨大学的饶舌歌手
and married a rapper who hates college.
Kourtney终于结束了
And Kourtney finally ended
与Scott之间消极的感情关系
her destructive relationship with Scott.
与此同时 Kim通过一张自拍的孕后裸照
Meanwhile, Kim's firing back at the haters
回击了痛恨她的人
with a naked pregnancy selfie.
慢着 我是怎么知道这一切的
Wait, how do I know all this?
我是在平时的新闻上看到的 还用说
I saw it on the regular news. Dah!
你的眼睛在迪斯科灯光下看上去好美
Your eyes look so pretty in the disco lights.
什么
What?
看上去不错哦 红发美女
Oh, looking good, Red.
Lillian 这对我有什么帮助
Lillian, how is this helping me?
我要找个新男友
I need to find a new boyfriend.
Dong已经结婚了
Dong is married.
没错 但这是假结婚
Yeah, but it's just a sham marriage
就像Titus和Vonda一样
like Titus and Vonda
林肯总统和她夫人也一样
or Abe Lincoln, Mary Todd.
政治婚姻
Political!
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
有些事情本身就是错的
Some things are just wrong,
比如亲吻一个已婚的人
like kissing a married person
或者追逐一样东西却声称它是送上门来的
or tracing something and saying you drew it.
Kimmy
Kimmy...
我们纽约这里有个非常好的东西
We have a wonderful thing here in New York
叫做道德相对主义
called moral relativism.
在你家乡 中西部
Where you're from, in the Midwest,
人们会说 "我从来没有对我妻子不忠"
people say, "I'll never cheat on my wife,"
或者说 "我不是同性恋
or, "I'm not gay.
我是摔跤教练"
I'm a wrestling coach."
然而有一天 嘣
And then one day, boof,
一切都崩溃了
the wheels come off,
他们在一个周末内把什么都做了 然后死了
they do it all in one weekend, and drop dead.
在这里 我们会说
Here, we say,
电影<皮革酒吧>与同志地下SM文化有关
"我只是在皮革酒吧里亲吻了一个牧师
"Eh, so I kissed a priest in a leather bar.
我伤害到谁了吗"
Who am I hurting?"
不 我不喜欢那样
No, I don't like that.
真是一场灾难啊
What a disaster.
如果你想要三明治 当然可以拿走
If you want the sandwich, take the sandwich, of course.
好吧 再见
Okay, bye-bye.
别管对错 去吧
Right, wrong, ehh.
你的骨骼比Sonja健壮许多
You have so many more bones than Sonja.
我以前经常喝很多奶粉
I used to eat a lot of powdered milk.
好吧 再见了 祝你生活美满
Okay, bye. Have a nice life.
我不敢相信你们竟然骗我
I can't believe you lied to me.
对不起 但我们也不知道该拿你怎么办
I'm sorry, but we don't know what to do with you anymore.
两起筒仓爆炸 怎么回事
Two silo explosions? How?
如果我知道的话 就不会发生第二次了
If I knew, it wouldn't have happened twice.
Jackie Lynn 我们小镇承受不起这样的损失
Jackie Lynn, our town can't afford this.
我们手里的钱少得可怜
We have so little money as it is.
汗屋仪式: 北美印第安人传统祭祀仪式 其形式类似于桑拿浴
长者们准备今晚举行汗屋仪式
The elders are having a sweat tonight
为Jackie Lynn的处境祈求最终决议
to pray for a resolution to the Jackie Lynn situation.
- 我想去  - 不行
- I want to go. - No.
给我远离汗屋
Stay away from the sweat lodge.
Jackie Lynn 你现在属于另一个部落了
Jackie Lynn, you belong to another tribe now.
什么意思
What does that mean?
也许你应该回纽约去
Maybe you should go back to New York.
好吧
Well... okay.
如果你们是这样想的
If that's the way you feel.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我把梦魇射向你们
I'm shooting nightmares at you.
这东西不是这样用的
That's not how it works.
捕梦网: 印第安人相信它可以"捕捉"好梦 阻挡噩梦
这是捕梦网
An ihanbla gmunka.
它象征着相互连通
It symbolizes connectivity.
就算只有一条线断了
If even one thread breaks,
整个捕梦网也就四分五裂了
everything falls apart.
就像你一样 Jackie Lynn
It's like you, Jackie Lynn.
你需要修复自己的网
You need to mend your web.
可你的人脉联系在曼哈顿
But your connections are back in Manhattan.
我在这个家做什么都不对
Nothing I ever do is good enough for this family.
Rob Kardashian: 金卡戴珊的弟弟
我觉得我就像Rob Kardashian
I feel like Rob Kardashian!
内个袜子设计师
The sock designer?
我为什么会知道这个
Why do I know that?
师傅 绕着这街区转两圈吧
Driver, just go around the block a few times.
噢 好吧
Oh. Right.
不
No.
不 不
No. No.
囚犯锁锁上了
The prisoner locks.
这儿和汗屋一样热
It's like a sweat lodge in here.
救命
Help!
咖啡
Coffee!
蠢白人
White idiot!
White idiot.
*我的披萨狂欢*
*Pizza party for one*
*离婚 死亡 真好玩*
*Divorced, dead, and having some fun*
*我的披萨狂欢*
*Pizza party for one*
我没买披萨
I don't have pizza.
干嘛 Kim Blake Nelson
What's wrong, Kim Blake Nelson?
我不知道 Titus 什么是错的
I don't know, Titus. What is wrong?
什么才是对的呢
And what's right?
什么是 耶
And what's just... ehh?
我发现生活大多处于灰色地带
I find that life is mostly gray areas,
我涂润肤乳时够不到的部位就变灰了
especially the parts I can't reach with moisturizer.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
这就是你对Vonda那么刻薄的理由吗
Is that why you thought it was okay to be so mean to Vonda?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're referring to,
反正在我看过的电影里
because in the movie I saw,
我是个奔波于各地为年轻的同性恋群体
I was a hero scoring a legal victory
赢得合法化的男主人公
for young run-a-gays everywhere.
你还没跟她道歉
You couldn't even apologize to her.
Titus Andromedon这辈子不做三件事
There are three things Titus Andromedon does not do:
道歉 变装 微积分
apologies, drag, and calculus.
我觉得可能在你还是Ronald Wilkerson时
I'm beginning to think maybe you were a better person
你还算是个好人
back when you were Ronald Wilkerson.
管你怎么想 反正Ronald Wilkerson已经死了
Well, we'll never know 'cause Ronald Wilkerson's dead.
噢 你今天要做爱顶嘴先生咯
Oh, you are just Mr. Sassafras Jeans today.
这蠢名字成功激怒我了
That's a dumb name for how fierce I'm being right now.
我要和Ronald讲话
I want to talk to Ronald.
啥
What?
他是个好人
He was good and nice,
他肯定还在你身体的某个角落
and he's still in there somewhere.
我体内有很多分裂人格
I have many past lives inside me.
- 我要和Ronald讲话  - 不要
- I want to talk to Ronald. - No!
Titus Andromedon 让我和Ronald讲话
Titus Andromedon, let me speak to Ronald!
拜托 Ronald不想跟你讲话
Ronald don't want to talk, please.
刚刚是Murasaki说的 等下我再解释她是谁
That was Murasaki. I'll explain her later.
Ronald 你爱Vonda
Ronald, you loved Vonda.
滚开 小婊砸
Leave us alone, lassie!
噢 刚刚是谁
Ooh, who was that?
噢 啊
Ow. Aah!
我 我
I... I...
我确实不曾想要伤害Vonda Jeanne
I sure didn't want to hurt Vonda Jeanne.
我害怕面对她
I was scared to face her.
要是她不愿接受我的道歉怎么办
What if she wouldn't accept my apology?
闭嘴 Ronald 你这个蠢货
Shut up, Ronald, you nerd.
看到了吧
See?
我就知道
I knew it.
你得接受Ronald的存在 Titus
You need to embrace your Ronald, Titus.
为什么
For why?
为了我 现在我就是你的Vonda
For me. I'm your Vonda now.
我怎么知道你会不会打包跑路
How do I know you won't just pack up and run away from me?
也可能我不会啊
Because I probably won't.
现在能让我安静地享用火腿蛤蜊披萨了吗
Now, can I please eat my ham and clam pizza in peace?
不对
That's wrong.
这配料不对
Those toppings are wrong.
我同意 先给我20分钟
I will agree with you in 20 minutes.
不过没事 不是吗
But it doesn't matter, does it?
这里是纽约
'Cause this is New York,
每个人都在道德上是相对的
where everyone's moral relatives.
你只要点份深盘火腿蛤蜊披萨
Just order a deep-dish ham/clam,
某个死变态就会给你做
and some sicko will make it for you.
我得让你知道我没点这个
I'll have you know I didn't order these.
我捡的
I found them.
我是这个城市里唯一一个
Am I the only person in this city
不那么随便的人吗
who doesn't just do whatevs whenevs?
干他妈的糖
Well, fudge that sugar.
让它见鬼去吧
Fudge it to heck,
长着一千根小鸡鸡的魔鬼
where a demon with a thousand wee-wees
会干死它
fudges it forever!
我要毁了Dong的早午饭
I'm crashing Dong's brunch!
我在这儿热得跟个印第安人一样
I'm sweating like an Indian in here.
没事 我可以这么说
It's okay. I can say that.
我可以说
I can say that.
Jackie Lynn 圆环象征着团结
Jackie Lynn, the hoop symbolizes unity.
我出现幻觉了
I'm visioning.
我们没有那么多的钱
We have so little money as it is.
你家房子在那边 蠢货
Your house is that way, dummy.
现在你属于另一个部族了
You belong to a different tribe now.
我扭 我扭 我扭扭扭
Boogie oogie, oogie.
玉米之神 你真是个电动玉米
Corn god. You are corn-lectric.
戴上你的隐形眼镜
Just use your contacts.
你的人脉联系在曼哈顿
Your connections are back in Manhattan.
在曼哈顿
In Manhattan...
我怎么还只是个物品
How am I still a thing?
- 联系  - 回曼哈顿
- Connections. - Back in Manhattan.
曲棍球是我们发明的
Lacrosse is our thing.
隐形眼镜 隐形眼镜
Contacts, contacts, contacts.
我知道我该做什么了
I know what I have to do!
Kimmy
Kimmy!
我是GED课上的Sonja
It's Sonja from GED class?
卡通版Anastasia公主就是关于我的
Also, the cartoon Anastasia is about me.
当然了 Sonja
Of course. Sonja.
你好
Hello.
Kimmy是我们最好的朋友
Kimmy is our best friend.
哦
Oh.
你当时参加了他们的婚礼吗
Were you at their wedding?
我本来想去的
Well, I wanted to be,
可这两只爱情鸟私奔了
but these two lovebirds eloped.
我今天可不是爱情鸟哟
I'm not a bird today.
Kimmy
Kimmy.
- 你在干  - 听着
- What are you-- - Listen.
我要和你私下聊聊
I need to talk to you in private.
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
听着 我们昨晚过得很开心 对吗
Look it, we had fun last night, right?
对 不过后来就很诡异了
Yeah. But then things got weird.
像Kourtney把母乳喷到
Like when Kourtney squirted
Kim的牛皮癣上那样诡异
her breast milk on Kim's psoriasis.
我怎么会知道这个
Why do I know about that?
重点来了
Here's the thing:
生活中有些灰色地带
there are gray areas in life.
Sonja的牛皮癣面积超大
Sonja's is enormous.
听着 我知道我们都想做对的事
Look, I know we both want to do the right thing,
但同样我也迫不及待让我的生活
but I also can't wait anymore for my life to...
- 等下  - 开始
- Stop. - ...start.
死掉的蠹虫
Dead silverfish.
我觉得这打虫药挺管用的
I guess the poison's working.
噢 现在又有一只在你头发里了
Oh, now there's one in your hair.
等着
Hang on.
Kimmy 不
Kimmy, no.
我们不能这么做
We can't do this.
听着 我来自中西部
Look, I'm from the Midwest.
我懂婚姻的圣洁
I believe in the sanctity of marr--
蠹虫
Silverfish.
但我想和你亲热 这样我才不会崩溃
But I also want to rub my mouth on your mouth so I don't boof.
等下
Stop it.
我要的不过是不被驱逐出境 就这样
All I want is not to be deported. That's it.
那昨晚怎么回事
What about last night?
昨晚是个错误
Last night was a mistake.
Lillian的头发看起来像面条一样
Lillian's hair looked like noodles.
我被缠住了
I got caught up in it.
如果移民署的那位女士也很爱滑旱冰呢
What if the immigration lady was also super into roller-skating?
我可能会失去一切
I could have lost everything.
- 但是  - 我觉得你该走了
- But-- - I think you should leave.
也许两年后再见吧
Maybe I'll see you in two years, then?
Titus 你在干嘛呢
Titus, what are you doing?
哇 只不过吵了一架你就要走吗
Wow, so one fight and you're out of here?
我失去了我的工作 男朋友
I've lost my job, my boyfriend,
我最喜欢的发带 现在连你也要走了吗
my favorite scrunchie, and now you?
我不想说这个 Kimmy
I don't want to talk about this, Kimmy.
我就是小题大做
I'm being dramatical.
好 你走
Fine. Go ahead.
再次逃避你的问题吧
Just run away from your problems... again.
你不能永远逃避问题的 Titus
You can't keep running away forever, Titus.
噢 我要紧紧跟着你
Oh, I will keep following you.
你知道我是对的
You know I'm right!
你的罪恶感会伴随你一生一世
Your guilt will chase you wherever you go.
你逃不了的 Titus
You can't escape, Titus!
去比洛克西的火车开了吗
Has the train to Biloxi left yet?
还没 晚点两个小时
Nope. It's running two hours late.
Vonda
Vonda!
等等
Wait!
等下 Vonda
Wait. Vonda?
天啊 谢天谢地车还没开
Boy, good thing the train was late.
哈 你觉得我们仅仅只是列车公司吗
Ha. You think we're a train company?
我们故意延迟发车的
We run late on purpose
这样人们就能以一种浪漫的方式找到彼此了
so people can find each other in romantical fashion.
Amtrak: 美国国家铁路客运公司
美铁 为爱而生
Amtrak... is for lovers.
Phillip
Phillip?
Sheila
Sheila.
Vonda 我很抱歉
Vonda... I'm sorry.
我们之间的友谊那么深切真实
The friendship we had was deep and real,
我不该以那种方式丢下你
and I should've never abandoned you that way.
可能这就是为什么我不找你的缘故吧
Maybe that's why I never called,
我怕知道我伤你多深
'cause I was afraid to hear how much I had hurt you.
不过如果你还肯要我
But if you'll have me,
我愿意做你的朋友
I'd like to be your friend...
不打炮
without benefits.
我愿意
I'd like that.
现在 我还想还你一些
And now, I'd like to pay you back
我欠你的东西
a little of what I owe you.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
第一次
for the first time anywhere,
Vonda Jeanne Brooks
Ms. and Mr. Vonda Jeanne Brooks
和Titus Ronald Wilkerson-Andromedon-Yoshimura
and Titus Ronald Wilkerson-Andromedon-Yoshimura.
我等下会解释
I'll explain that later.
*嘿 宝贝*
*Hey, baby*
*你要记住*
*You got to remember*
*你知道我*
*You know I am*
Dong
Dong.
种族歧视啊
Racist.
Karen
Karen.
嘿
Hey.
*你听过这些故事吗*
*Have you been hearin' the stories?*
*故事在流传*
*They're goin' around*
*朋友们都在讲*
*All of my friends are talking*
*宝贝 记住我的心在你身上*
*Baby, just remember I gave you my heart *
*没人可以拆散我们*
*Ain't no one gonna tear us apart*
*他对着月亮*
*He could promise the moon*
*和天上的星星宣誓*
*And the stars above*
*即使他已宣誓给我一切*
*Even if he promised me the world*
*记住我永远你是你的女孩*
*Just remember I'm forever your girl*
*他对着全世界宣誓*
*He could promise the world*
*你要记住*
*You got to remember*
*我看见她*
*I saw her*
*在曼哈顿的月光下*
*Under the Manhattan moon*
*你就在那儿*
*There you were*
*蜷在小船上*
*Crouching by your rowboat*
*靠近中央公园的小湖边*
*Near the Central Park lagoon*
*你卷曲的发丝*
*Your hair was so curly*
*乌黑的眼睛*
*Your eyes were so black*
*确实让我心跳加速*
*Of course it made my heart beat faster*
*卟卟卟卟卟卟*
*Bub-bub-bub-bub-bub-bub*
*我一开始就知道*
*I knew from the start*
*你会把我伤得体无完肤*
*That you'd break my heart*
*还有打嗝*
*And the burping*
*真是灾难*
*What a disaster*
*我爱你*
*I love you*
*即使我像个笨蛋般疯狂*
*Even though I'm crazy as a loon*
*但这些都是相对的*
*But it's all relative*
*让我们相互宽容*
*Yeah, it's live and let live*
*有时候*
*Sometimes*
*在曼哈顿月色*
*Under the Manhattan*
*之下*
*Moon*
嗯
Mm.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组